mycorporation.com 2013-10-24

# Privacy | MyCorporation®

## Get more information about our privacy policies.

At MyCorporation, we place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. Our most important asset is our relationship with you. We want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our Web site. Therefore, we would like to share with you the following principles that govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our Web site. This privacy statement defines privacy aspects specific to MyCorporation.com. Throughout this policy, we refer to information that personally identifies you as "personal information."

### We protect your information

We work to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards. We use both internal and external resources to review our security procedures. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information.

### We tell you how we use your information

When we ask you for information, we will tell you, or it will be clear, what we need to know to fulfill your request and how the information you provide us will be used. For example, if you request a service from us, we will ask you for your name and contact information such as, mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address. In addition to responding to your request, we may use your contact information to tell you about products or services we think might interest you or to invite you to participate in a product or service-related survey. Because of the financial nature of our business, our Web sites are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly request or receive any information from children.

  * We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.
  * We do not share your personal information with anyone outside of MyCorporation for their promo

### We tell you about our relationships with third parties

We have limited relationships with third parties to assist us in servicing you, for example, by fulfilling customer orders or providing customer service. These service providers are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide them. Additionally, we have business partners that provide services, some of which are co-branded. We clearly identify partner services and sites. When you request any of these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your personal information to the partner to fulfill your dynamoRequest. We may disclose your information if we are required to by a law enforcement action such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant. 

### We tell you how we use Web technology

Like many Web sites, we use technology, such as cookies, that allow us to make your visit to our Web site easier by recognizing you when you return and help to provide you with a customized experience. 

### We give you choice and control

We may use your contact information to tell you about other products we think might interest you. However, if you don't want us to contact you for promotional purposes, you can tell us when you provide the information. Your contact preferences only apply to marketing contact. We may need to communicate with you regarding service communications, legally mandated notices, and critical messages that could impact your business.

At any time you may request to update or correct your personal, corporate or financial information by calling MYCORP **toll-free at 1-888-MY-CORP-1** or contacting us through our website at MyCorporation.

**To unsubscribe from MyCorporation marketing communications** , please email [customersupport@mycorporation.com](mailto:customersupport@mycorporation.com?subject=Unsubscribe%20Me) and include the words "Unsubscribe Me" in the subject line.

### Privacy Protection

We protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. Whenever we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we encrypt it as it is transmitted to us.

Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

### Services

  * **Order Processing:** The personal information that is collected to process your order might include contact information (name, mailing address, telephone number, fax number and/or email address); corporate information (business name and description of business, information regarding directors, officers, members, stockholders and registered agent and information regarding shares of stock and par value); and financial information (checking account, name on account, credit card number and expiration date), depending upon the nature of your order.

The contact information, corporate information and financial information from the order form are used to process your request and to contact you for purposes of completing the services requested. Financial information that is collected is used for billing purposes and is not shared with anyone outside of our company, except the merchant bank for the processing of credit card orders, the product delivery service, and the state office to which the requested documents will be submitted.

  * **Status Page:** Information relating to the status of an order, including only the corporate name and status of the requested service will be displayed on a "status page" of the mycorporation.com site.

### Web Technology

We use a variety of technologies on our Web site. Among these are cookies, which are pieces of information that our Web sites provide to your browser. Cookies allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer. Cookies also allow us to customize your visit to our Web site by recognizing you when you return. You can choose to decline cookies while at our Web site, however, this may limit your ability to access certain areas of the Web site. Most browsers accept and maintain cookies by default. Check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preference.

When we track activity on this Web sites, we collect information such as your IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you get to our sites and any links you click on to leave our sites. We do not track non-MyCorporation URLs that you type into your browser, nor do we track you across the Internet once you leave our sites. We use your Web site activity to assist you by reducing the need to re-enter your data and to help us resolve technical support issues. We may also use this information to offer you a personalized Web experience, and to tailor our offerings to you. Remember, you control whether you receive MyCorporation promotional materials.

We may access and set cookies using Web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs which are invisible graphical images. These Web beacons tell us useful information regarding our site such as which pages users access. When we send you e-mails, we may include a single-pixel GIF to determine the number of people who open our e-mails. When you click on a link in an e-mail, we record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you.

Advertising networks that serve ads on our Web site may assign a different cookie to you. The information collected is anonymous and is not linked to your personal information. These cookies may be used to select which ads you see and determine the effectiveness of this advertising. You may choose to decline cookies from third-party ad servers, which MyCorporation does not control. If you would like to know more about this practice and your choices about not having this information used by third-party ad servers, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

### More about our relationships with third parties

Sometimes, we enter into contracts with third parties who assist us in servicing you such as filling customer orders or providing customer service. The contracts outline the appropriate use and handling of your information and prohibit third parties from using any of your personal information for purposes unrelated to the product or service for which they've been contracted. Vendors are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or a law enforcement dynamoRequest.

We have business partners that provide services, some of which are co-branded. Partner services and sites are clearly identified. When you request any of these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your personal information to the partner to fulfill your dynamoRequest. This Web site may provide links to third-party sites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. Because MyCorporation does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personal information.

Should we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will have the opportunity to ask not to receive promotional information following any change of control.

We may use sources outside of MyCorporation to supplement the information you give us. For example, we may validate your address using other sources. We use this data to help us maintain accuracy and provide you with better service.

MyCorporation Business Services Inc. may exchange information about your transactions to fulfill your requests. We may also provide you information about products or services we believe you may be interested in unless you have asked us not to contact you. We offer you the opportunity to review privacy practices at our subsidiaries' Web sites. Please visit Intuit for additional information on our subsidiaries.

Back To Top
